<resources>
    <string name="app_name">V!P</string>
    <string name="signup"><u>Don\'t have an account? Sign up</u></string>
    <string name="passwdf"><u>Forgot Password?</u></string>

    <string name="aboutus">SAVA is a self proclaimed name given by the developers of this software application consisting of the initials of their names.
        SAVA has not yet came into market,it earns no profit from any other organisation.

        At SAVA, we understand your problems and requirements equally and hence we bring out our Vehicle in Pursuit(VIP) app to resolve vehicle details queries and many more required
        features to set a beautiful relation between traffic police and the public with just a click.

    </string>

    <string name="contactus">For further details, Contact us at :\n\n\n
                        Email us at :\n
                                anandkumarsinha07@gmail.com,\n
                                subodhsgujar@gmail.com,\n
                                ashishdjee@gmail.com\n\n
                        Call us at :\n
                                Anand Sinha : 8788472498,\n
                                Vedant Ingole : 9403170823\n
        </string>

    <string name="terms">
        ● The content on this app app is meant for sharing information regarding vehicles on the basis of available information on Vehicle National Register.\n

● Using content of this app for any commercial purpose or any derivative work or misuse of any kind is strictly prohibited and may invite legal consequences.\n

● The content can be removed from the portal without notice and at anytime as per Ministry of Road Transport Direction.\n

● Ministry of Road Transport and Highways/NIC shall not be held responsible for any interactions/passing of information(s) etc. between any user via e-mail,chat and any other mediation with another user.\n

● Ministry of Road Transport and Highways/NIC has no obligation to monitor any such disputes arising between the users and shall not be party to such dispute/litigation etc.\n

● These terms and condition shall be governed by and constructed in accordance with the Indian Laws.\n

● Any dispute arising under these terms and conditions shall be subject to the jurisdiction of the courts of Indian only.\n
    </string>

    <string name="polFunctionalities">
        \n\n<u><b>What can Police do through V!P ?</b></u>\n\n
        -Police requires a valid police id to get registered and get logged in to use this app for checking vehicle information and taking further legal actions.\n

        -Police can automatically send the vehicle towed location to the vehicle owner.\n\n
Information Retrieval after vehicle search:\n

● Owner Name\n

● Contact number\n

● Address\n

● Maker Info\n

● Registration date\n

● Fuel type\n

● Vehicle age\n

● Registration authority\n


● Engine number\n

● Chassis number\n\n


    </string>

    <string name="pubFunctionalities">
        \n\n<u><b>What can Public do through V!P ?</b></u>\n\n
        -Public requires a valid mobile number to signup or logged in to the VIP app.\n
        -Public can search and retrieve details of their own vehicles as well as others.\n
        -Public is also provided a complaint feature in the app where they can issue a complain immediately in case their car has been stolen or robbed.\n\n

Information retrieval after vehicle search:\n

● Owner Name\n

● Maker Info\n

● Registration date\n

● Fuel type\n

● Vehicle age\n

● Registration authority\n
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
